hideme.be 2014-11-15

# HideMe - Free Web Proxy & Anonymous Surfing

Home | [Anonymous Email](http://email.hideme.be/) | My Ip Address | How To Stay Anonymous | FAQ | Contact

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At HideMe we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

It is HideMe’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, HideMe collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. HideMe’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how HideMe’s visitors use its website. From time to time, HideMe may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Service logs

The service provided on this website allows access to external, third-party websites. We may record your IP address and the websites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

HideMe does not asks or store any personally-identifying information. 

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

HideMe discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on HideMe’s behalf or to provide services available at HideMe’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using HideMe’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. HideMe will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, HideMe discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when HideMe believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of HideMe, third parties or the public at large. HideMe takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. HideMe uses cookies to help HideMe identify and track visitors, their usage of HideMe website, and their website access preferences. HideMe visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using HideMe’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of HideMe’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the websites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party website. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option.

* For more information on configuring your browser, see [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1) or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites.

## Business Transfers

If HideMe, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that HideMe goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of HideMe may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by HideMe and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, HideMe may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in HideMe’s sole discretion. HideMe encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. 

**Change log:**

  * _January 3, 2011:_ Added court order

  * Home
  * Edit Browser
  * Cookies
  * Privacy Policy
  * Disclaimer
  * Terms of Use
  * FAQ
